Guide to the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, General Committee of the New York Central Railroad (Lines West), chairman's files, 1909-1962 [bulk 1931-1962].
- 13. Work Claims and Disputes.
  Materials on work claims and disputes (1951-1963) include grievances (1957-1963) regarding wages, seniority, working conditions, safety matters, craft jurisdiction, fringe benefits, overtime, promotion, discipline, dismissal, overtime, meal expense, and theft (company and personal) (1957-1965); minutes of BRS state legislative representatives (1956-1961); report on activities of state legislative representatives of BRS (1953-1955); a petition to Congress urging the repeal of the portion of the Railway Labor Act which permits negotiation of union shop agreements; letters regarding veterans' reemployment rights (1953-1963); claims by the United Railroad Operating Crafts that it is a national organization and entitled to participate in selection and designation of National Railroad Adjustment Board (NRAB) labor members (1958); application of union shop agreement to veterans and those on leave of absence; validity of union shop amendment and union shop agreement; also circular letters from Jesse Clark regarding federal legislation affecting railroad employees (1958-1960); and the Railroad Yardmasters of America organizing campaign within the New York Central system.
  - Awards Made By Special Board of Adjustment (1-5) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CTC Project (1960) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Employee Self-Discipline as a Part of Education and Accident Prevention Program (1958) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Consolidation of Ohio Division and Ohio Central Div. Seniority Roster (1962) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Expense Claims (Elkhart Signal Shop 1955-62) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Time and Half Pay Claim (1963) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Petty Larceny - Personal File (1962) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Complaint About Denial of Claims Indianapolis Union Railroad (1963) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Automatic Snow Collectors (1962) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Working Conditions (1961-63) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Discipline Hearing. Employee's Failure to Inspect Relay Circuit Resulting in Accident (1962) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Removal of Positions, Sheldon, 111. (1962) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Inspector-Foremen Membership in Craft Locals (1962) Dues (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Federal Legislation Concerning Railroad Employees (1958-60) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rate of Pay for 'Maintainers in Charge' (1943-51) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - R.L. Nunn - Disciplinary Action (1962) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Splicing Work Done by Leading Signal Mechanic (1962) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Testing Highway Crossing Signals in Canada (1958) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Inspector-Foremen Performing Craft Work (1958) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - I.H.B. - Labor Relations (1959-63) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Accident Liability Benefit Claims (1960-62) (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Transfer of Signal Sections (1958) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Change in Managerial Jurisdiction (North District) 1958 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Discipline Case (1961-62) (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - NRAB (1961-62) (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Personal Injury Claim (1962) (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Work Jurisdiction (1953 and 1961) (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 15 - Company Trucks (1962-63) (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Work Jurisdiction Claim (1961) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Seniority Rights (1962) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Differential Pay Rates for Craft Employees (1962) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Transfer of Maintenance Sections from Illinois (P and E) to Indiana Division (1961) (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Agreement including Hot Box Defectors (1962) (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Position Bid and Expense Claim (1961-62) (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Suspension as Discipline (1961) (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - State Legislative Counsels (1952-61) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Supplemental 3rd Division, NRAB (1958-61) (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Sanford Mullins vs. NYC Railroad (1961-63) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - NYC/IHB Agreement (claims and correspondence 1960-61) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Work Holiday at Straight Time (1960) (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Clarification of Memorandum of Craft Agreement, Gang Assignments (1961) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Force Reduction due to Picketing of the NYC by Maritime Unions (1961). (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - UROC (United Railroad Operating Crafts) (1958) (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Abolishment of Cleveland Signal District and Allocation of Seniority Rights (1960-61) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Veteran's Re-employment Rights (1953-62) (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Application of Vacation and Holiday Pay Rules (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Representation Authorization Form (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Consolidation of Locals 30 and 11, Ohio Division (1954-60) (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Stealing Tools from Trucks (1960) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Duplicate Claims (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - LMRDA of 1959 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - 1959-60 Agreement - Wages and Vacations (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Claim - C.G. Spencer (1960) (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Toilet Facilities at Michigan City (1961) (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Transfer of Signal Sections to Toledo Signal District (1957) (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Forced Promotions of Assistants (1960) (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Electronic Technicians (1961) (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - P and E, Illinois Division; Transfer of Positions (1961) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - NYC Incorporated in State of Delaware (1961) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Lateness of Paychecks (1961-63) (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Protesting Headquarters (1960-61) (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Transfer of District from Chicago Terminal to Indiana Div. (1960-61) (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Levermen's Desire to Join Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen (1963) (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Wage Request - 1963 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Hydro-Crane - Purchase and Operation of (1963) (Box 10, Folder 69)
- 15. Union Shop.
  Materials on the union shop include transcripts of hearings on union shop agreement violations (1952-1962), among related documents.
  - NYC; M.C. Big Four Agreement (1951) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - P and LE (1951) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - I.G.R. Railroad (1951) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Case Files on Union Shop Agreement (1951-55) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Hiring and Firing (1951) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Local Financial Secretaries (1951-63) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Termination of Employment (1952-59) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Removals from Service - New York Central (1957-60) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Big 4 (1952-53) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - P and LE (1952-57) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Michigan Central (1951-60 ) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Michigan Central Big 4 Indiana Division (1951-6951-62) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-56) New York Central (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-56) Big 4 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions(1951-62) I.H.B. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-55) Michigan Central (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Local 83 Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-53) New York Central (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Local 96 Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-52) New York Central (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Local 128 Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1951-56) New York Central (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Local 210 Employment (Reinstatement) Reductions (1952-56) New York Central (Box 11, Folder 20)
- 19. Travelers Insurance Company.
  Materials on the Travelers Insurance Company (1951-1963) include transcripts of hearings on the health and welfare movement, among related documents.
- 20. Miscellaneous.
  - I.H.B. 1951 Agreement (1954-55) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Revision to I.H.B. Agreement (1953) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Resolutions (1961) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - New York Central (1959-63) Local Wiring Work (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - P and LE Employee Seniority (1953-54) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - P and LE Miscellaneous Correspondence and Agreements (1951-57) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - New York Central - Income Accounts (1932-33) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Agreements (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Foreman Agreements (1931-33) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - General Electric Company (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Wage and Force Reductions (1930-34) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Railway Labor Executive Association (1932-33) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Maintainer Units (1930-32) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 35th Regular Convention (1961) (Box 12, Folder 8)
- 21. Reduced Work Week.
  - New York Central (1932-38) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Big Four (1935) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NRAB Cases (1938) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ballots on the Work Week (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - I. H. B. Railroad (1931 - 35) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Report of General Chairman (1933-38) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New York Central Railroad - Working Time (1932-34) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - I.H.B. (1935-36) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Schedules (1930-38) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Michigan Central (1931-34) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Signal Inspection Law (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Third Division, NRAB Settlement of Work Week (Box 13, Folder 12)
- 22. Miscellaneous.
  - 1942 Wage Controversy (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Wage Increase - 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Directory of General Chairman (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - PANIC Merger - Text of Agreement (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - PANYC Merger - Related Correspondence (1962-63) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - PANYC Merger - Related Publications (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Record Books (Box 15)
  - Phonodiscs, pamphlets, record book, etc. (Box 16)